Hello friends, you are very welcome
in today's video of mine, many people
buy the policy from the market
but they do
not inspect the infection inside the vehicles with the help of video, the
reason is that sometimes there are so many
qualifications
that when flowers are offered here, some have
problems, then it is not considered complete, so
brother, if you are
giving darshan in this, in the case of a car policy in two
wheeler, in many cases, but it is
mandatory, in the room,
in the head of the idol,
how to do it,
I had purchased the insurance policy of this vehicle online from the market,
but you have to see
when you have to upload it inside the app, so
brother, the first thing in the app is to
open your Bullet, all the
windows should be opened, you have to
sit on the driver's seat, the RC and the old
insurance should be in your hand, the keys should be
inside the vehicle, now we
start it, sitting on the
driver's seat, move forward,
which should be requested from inside, now give you ghee
and while moving it from top to bottom,
use the first thing in the whole world  Do not do it from
top to bottom like this and from top to
bottom left side
that national always has to do it like this
request the position from both front and back sides
Vikramaditya's both sides can be read clearly
now we will move it forward as per
first of all this is
very important
now we will do it like this so it is done
I am free from voice let's move to second page
Ajay
and the second page is also done yes let's go he will
keep this 30 and we have to
determine it takes time for the scanner camera to
focus that it was
important that he has a normal train
this is the phone so he is doing it quickly so by doing this
you have to scan all the subjects
Akshay will back arm
this button so
what do I tell you
record the call audio manager is the
total distance travelled by your car there is
some blur also make sure that you are
not recording any nocturnal emission
because this can develop your video do
not do ghee now start it again like this
we will move the car now if there is
another number then please
you have to record this video this looted  The
front key has to be pressed,
A
firecracker
compartment means loot,
this point has to be done, bank, now see
what is being made, before that, with the water of Puri, right, that is, A, I was
lying on the right hand,
up and down, 9, I have done that,
I have to do
2308, in
this, stay, this is yours,
now inside this, we have
woven some empire from all sides, you have done it,
Ajay has
flight, behind, ₹50 in detail and then the key
runs, Ajay's number plate is
A1,
that you have completed all the steps of recording,
if you have forgotten to record any step, is it
not working correctly, you can do it even now,
you can do
a lesson, okay, you can check from here by
playing it like this, whether you have played all the things, whether everything has to be
recorded correctly
or not, okay, record all,
check all the recordings,
after that submit, okay, or it will take a little
time to get the plot done, it will not take much,
whatever it will take, net will be required, let's do a little bit of
your work, so
brothers, this is how we do the policy market's
width video inspection